A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Constituent Correspondence of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder,
1990.
The Library of Virginia
34142
Virginia. Governor (1990-1994: Wilder).
41 cu. ft. (41 boxes)
Administrative Information
Arranged by series.
Access Restrictions
These records are open for research but it may be necessary for an archivist to review certain files before they can be used by patrons for research purposes or before any copies of the records can be made. Privacy protected and other protected information is considered confidential and restricted from public access for 75 years. If you are planning to use these records, please contact Archives Reference Services for additional details before planning your research trip.
Acquisition Information
Accession 34142 was transferred by Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, April 22, 1992.
Historical Information
Lawrence Douglas Wilder was born in Richmond, Va., on January 17, 1931. He graduated from Virginia Union University in 1951 and afterwards was drafted into the Army, where he served in the Korean War from 1952-1953 and received a bronze star. He then attended the Howard University School of Law and graduated in 1959. Douglas Wilder was elected to the Virginia Senate in 1969 as the first African American member since Reconstruction and served in the Senate for five terms. In 1985, he was elected to the office of Lieutenant Governor as the first African American to be elected to statewide office in Virginia. L. Douglas Wilder won the election for Governor of Virginia in 1989 and served from January 13, 1990 to January 14, 1994. He was the first African American to be elected as Governor in United States.
The Office of Constituent Affairs was first established in 1984 to serve as a liaison between the Governor and the citizens of the Commonwealth. The Office oversees and coordinates responses to all mail sent to the Governor's Office. Constituent Affairs staff determine where and under whose signature the responses should be drafted and direct correspondence to the appropriate person in the administration. The Office also answers phone inquiries from constituents and occasionally meets with constituents to resolve problems and handle requests. William R. Browning served as Director of Constituent Affairs during the Wilder Administration.
Scope and Content
Constituent Correspondence, 1990, is housed in 41 boxes and consists of letters received by Governor Wilder from citizens, public officials, and various organizations. Correspondence in this series usually includes an accompanying Response Referral Form, and an attached copy of the response from the Governor or the appropriate Secretary, state agency, or Governor's Office staff member. The Response Referral Form includes date received, topic, to whom the letter is referred, and instructions. Constituent correspondence includes invitations, requests for assistance, and statements of concern or inquiries on a variety of issues. Constituent correspondence also includes limited correspondence from federal and state agencies, local government officials, Virginia General Assembly members, members of the U.S. Congress, and others, including the U.S. President, governors of other states, and ambassadors.
Constituent Correspondence, 1993, is divided into three series: Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies; Series II. Governor's Office; and Series III. Scheduling Office. Correspondence is arranged by topic and includes mail on a variety of subjects, including administration initiatives and specific legislative actions. Also includes mail from habitual writers, and mass mailings, which often consist of form letters and signed petitions.
Some topics of interest to constituents in 1990 include the death penalty, landfills and swan hunting.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1990
Series II. Governor's Office, 1990
Series III. Scheduling Office, 1990.
Contents List
- Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1990., Extent: 18 cubic feet (18 boxes). (Box 1-18)
  Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies correspondence, is housed in 18 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by Cabinet Secretary, and alphabetically by topic or state agency within each Secretarial area. This series includes correspondence received by the Governor's Office that was directed to Cabinet Secretaries or state agencies for response. Includes original letter, Response Referral Form, and attached response.
  - Secretary of Administration: Allocations of additional persons, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Administration: Allocations of additional persons, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Administration: Budget cuts, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Administration: Budget cuts, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Administration: Compensation Board, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Administration: Equal Employment Services, Office of, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Administration: Equal Employment Services, Office of, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Administration: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990 Feb-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990 May. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990 June. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990 July. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990 Aug. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990 Sept. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990 Oct. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Administration: General, 1990 Nov-Dec. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Administration: General Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Administration: Health Insurance and Benefits, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Administration: Human Rights, Council on, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Administration: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Administration: Land Information, Advisory Commission on, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Administration: Local Government, Commission on, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Administration: Purchase and Supply, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Administration: Veterans Affairs, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Administration: Veterans Affairs, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Administration: Veterans Affairs, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Retirement System, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Retirement System, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Retirement System, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Retirement System, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Retirement System, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture and Development Authority, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Auctions, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 16a)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Bloomingdales' Event, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Budget cuts, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Commerce, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Commission for the Arts, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Commission for the Arts, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Consumer Services, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Consumer Services, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Down zoning actions, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Economic Development, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Employment Commission, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Employment Commission, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Employment Commission, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Employment Commission, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Farmer's markets, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Festival of American Film, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Forestry, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Fruit crop disaster, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Developement, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Developement, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Developement, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Developement, Dept. of - Homelessness, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing Development Authority, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing Development Authority, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing Partnership Program, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Lucky Goldstar, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Minorty Business, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Real Estate, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Relocate in Virginia, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Rural Development, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Tour de Trump Bicycle Race, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Tourism, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Tourism, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: VEDCORP, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Port Authority, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Welcome Centers, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Welcome Centers, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Welcome Centers, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: World Trade, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: World Trade, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: World Trade, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education: Center for Innovative Technology, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education: Commission on Educational Opportunity in Virginia, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - Dropout prevention, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - Drug prevention, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - Drug prevention, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - Education Assistance Authority, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - School boards, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - School boards, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - School funding, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education: Education, Dept. of - Teacher salaries, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education: English Language Movement, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: Explorer's Project and Project Discovery, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Education: George Mason University, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Education: Governor's School Program, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Education: Gunston Hall, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Education: James Madison University, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Education: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Education: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Education: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Education: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Education: Longwood College, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education: National Air and Space Museum, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: Norfolk State University, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Education: Old Dominion University, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Education: Radford University, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Education: State budget cuts, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Education: State budget cuts, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Education: State budget cuts, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Education: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education: State Council on Higher Education for Virginia, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education: Science Museum of Virginia, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: Tidewater Community College, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: Tuition Assistance Grant, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education: University of Virginia, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education: University of Virginia, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education: University of Virginia, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education: University of Virginia, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education: University of Virginia, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Commonwealth University, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Commonwealth University, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Community College System, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Educational Loan Authority, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Military Institute, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Museum of Fine Art, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia State Library and Archives, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia State Library and Archives, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia State University, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: Vocational and industrial education, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: William and Mary, College of, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Finance: Accounts, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Finance: Cigarette tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Finance: Comptroller, Office of the, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Finance: Comptroller, Office of the, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Finance: Decision brief, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Finance: Economic Advisory Council, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Finance: Scheats, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Finance: Food tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Finance: Freedom Day tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Finance: Gasoline tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Finance: General, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Finance: General, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income and Assessment tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income and Assessment tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Finance: Income and assessment tax, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Finance: Internal auditors, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Finance: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Finance: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Finance: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Finance: Prescription drug prices, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Finance: Property taxes, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Finance: Retirement tax, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Finance: State Lottery proceeds, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Finance: Tax amnesty, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - State budget revenue, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - State budget revenue, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Finance: Treasury, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Abortion, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Abortion, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Adolescent Pregnancy Progrom, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Aging, Dept. for the, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Aid for Dependent Children, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Alcohol and drug abuse, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Certificate of Public Need, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Certificate of Public Need - Loudoun County petition, 1990. (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Children, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Council on Child Daycare and Early Childhood, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Council on Indians, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Council on the Status of Women, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Family Violence Prevention Program, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Governor's Employment and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Hard of Hearing, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of - General, 1989-1990. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources, Dept. of - General, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Professions, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Services Cost Review Council, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Services Cost Review Council, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: HIV and AIDS, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Job Training Partnership Act, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medicare, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medicare, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)